Hello friends, Namaskar, today let's
discuss about general insurance.  The
company has presented its quarter two numbers.
Let's see.  The company has
declared an interim dividend of ₹6.50 per share.  Whose record
date is 23 October 2025, which will be credited
to the share holder's account on 12 November 2025.
Talking about the company's revenue, the company had earned a
first year premium
of Rs 85255 lakh in the last quarter.  The company had
earned a premium of Rs 694830 lakh last year.  The company has
earned a premium of Rs 75836 lakh in this quarter.  The company's
premium is increasing year after year.
But a
decline is being seen quarter after quarter.  Talking about the company's
expenses, the company had spent Rs
5,42,923 lakh in the last quarter.  The
company had
spent Rs 518648 lakh last year.  The company has
spent Rs 5831 lakh in this quarter.   There is a
slight increase in the company's expenses.
Talking about the company's profit, the
company had made a
profit of Rs 74,708 lakh in the last quarter.  The company had made a
profit of Rs 79,395 lakh in the last quarter.  The
company has made a
profit of Rs 81,954 lakh in this quarter.  The company
's profits are increasing year after year and quarter after
quarter.
Talking about the company's EPS, the company's IPS was
₹14.92 in the last quarter.  The company's
IPS was ₹13.8 last year.  The company's
IPS is ₹16.35 in this quarter.  The company
's IPS is increasing year after year and quarter after
quarter.  That's all for today's
video.  Good luck watching the video
, sharing, commenting,
subscribing to the channel and
consult your financial advisor before investing.
Thank you.